Guide to the Joy Golden Papers, 1956-2012 RL.00461
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1979-2005 and undated, 13 boxes
  - Speeches
    - Chutzpah (Eagle Snacks: Columbus Ave.; Frobel: Craving/Hot Tub/Valley Girl; Pevely: Kezzy Boomer/Spiritual Experience; KPIX-TV: Affair; MS Readathon: Midget). 1988. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 9:00 (Box AV2)
    - College (Wheaties; Columbus Ave.; Craving; Aunt Lil; Allie's BBQ; Lanie's Wedding; Valley Girl; Cheapskate). 1994. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 8:00 (Box AV2)
    - Frobel/Kezzy (Frobel: Hot Tub Brunch/Picnic/Singles/Arnold's Mom/Divorce/Valley Girl/Craving; Pevely: Party Giver/Kezzy's Spiritual Experience). 1987. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 12:00 (Box AV2)
    - Montreal (Eagle Snacks: Anniversary/Columbus Ave.; Frobel: Sweet 16/Craving/Valley Girl; Granada: Cheapskate; KPIX: Vanity; Pevely: Kezzy Boomer; Alpine Lace: Jewish Deli). 1991. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 9:00 (Box AV2)
    - N.E. Ad Club (Eagle Snacks: Anniversary; Frobel: Craving/Valley Girl; Partnership for a Drug Free America: Lanie's Wedding; Alpine Lace: Jewish Deli/Pookins; Granada: Cheapskate; KPIX: Vanity; Pevely: Kezzy Boomer). 1991. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 11:00 (Box AV2)
    - Restaurant/Washington (Frobel: Craving; Valley Girl; Hot Tub Brunch; Uncle Hal). 1988. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV2)
    - Speech (Frobel: Craving/Valley Girl/Arnold's Mom/Enid and Galaxy; Pevely: Kezzy Boomer/Kezzy's Spiritual Experience; Beefsteak Charlie's: Ga Ga; SNET: Piano). 1987. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV2)
    - Speech (Money: Dentist; Granada TV: Cheapskate/Dial-a-Deal; Goldstar: Grunitiski/Low Class; Maxwell House: Sidewalk; S. New England Telephone: Sticky Stuff/Phoebe; Citibank: Appliance Store; Jefferson Bank: Gift). 1986. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV2)
    - Television Academy, 9 spots. 1986. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 9:00 (Box AV2)
  - Compilations
    - Reel 7 (City One; Evian; Goldstar; Our Magazine; Budweiser; Money Magazine; Wheel of Fortune; Hebrew National; Granada; Stressbuster; Jefferson Bank; La Cage Aux Folles; Eagle Snacks; Laughing Cow; SNE Telephone). 1985. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 13:00 (Box AV3)
    - Reel 14 (Frobel; Granada; Pevely; Eagle Snacks; Coca-Cola; Wall Street Journal; SNET; La Cage Aux Folles; KPIX; Partnership for a Drug Free America; Blue Star; Beefsteak Charlie's; Citibank; Carlsberg; Bryant Park; Goldstar). Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 26:00 (Box AV3)
    - Reel 16 (Eagle Snacks; Granada; Pevely; Pealer's; Frobel; Alpine Lace; WNBC; KPIX; Wall Street Journal; Blue Star; Partnership for a Drug Free America; Carlsberg). 1991. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 18:00 (Box AV3)
    - Reel 17: Golden Oldies and Newies. 1991. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 20:00 (Box AV3)
    - Reel 18: Golden Oldies and Newies Revisited. 1992. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 20:00 (Box AV3)
    - Reel 20 (Frobel; KPIX; Eagle Snacks; Goldstar; Pevely; Partnership for a Drug Free America; Evian; Granada TV Rental; Hebrew National; Carlsberg; La Cage Aux Folles; KPIX). 1994. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 14:00 (Box AV3)
    - Reel 21 (Automatic Data Processing; WKYC TV; Allie's BBQ; Milkbone; Blue Cross Blue Shield; Shoetown; Love Connection; WNBC; SNET; Alpine Lace; Catskills on Broadway). 1994. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 11:00 (Box AV3)
    - Comedy reel/Music reel. 1985. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 20:00 (Box AV3)
    - Comedy in Radio Montage. 1991. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 20:00 (Box AV3)
    - Dottie's Best Schott (Pizza Hut; 8 O'Clock Coffee; Goldstar; Ladies Home Journal; Evian; KYC TV; Opti -Free Lens Care; Cutter repellent; Lillet Wine; Medi-Quick; Sterling Jewelers; Carlsberg; KPIX). Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 14:00 (Box AV3)
    - Friar's (Stan Freeberg; Craving; Art Collector; Lanie's Wedding; Catskills Aunt Lil; Mabel Blue Cross; VG1; Columbus Ave.; Dear Jerry Herman; Doctor Catskills). 1993. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV3)
    - Radio spots of all kinds, reel 1 (Tijuca Beer; Laughing Cow; Eagle Snacks; Domestica; Money Magazine; LA Beer; Marriott; KDKA; Stressbuster; Maxwell House; Elephant Malt Liquor; Pizza Hut; Jefferson Bank; Hebrew National; Signal; Fresh Chef). 1991. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 34:00 (Box AV3)
    - Radio spots of all kinds, reel 2 (Pizza Hut; Elephant Malt Liquor; Laughing Cow; Dining Lite; Signal; Eagle Snacks; Ladies Home Journal; Atlantis; La Cage Aux Folles; Hebrew National; Fresh Chef; Budweiser; Goldstar; SNET; Money Magazine; Blue Star; Jefferson Bank; Granada; LA Beer). 1991. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 35:00 (Box AV3)
    - Spots from Sound Patrol, reel 1 (Wall Street Journal; KPIX; Carlsberg; Frobel; Eagle Snacks; Alcon; Pevely; Coca-Cola; Granada TV; La Cage Aux Folles; Partnership for a Drug Free America; Blue Star; First Investors; Bryant Park; SNET; Goldstar; Beefsteak Charlies's; Hebrew National). Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 31:00 (Box AV3)
    - Spots from Sound Patrol, reel 2 (Wall Street Journal; KPIX; Carlsberg; Frobel; Eagle Snacks; Pevely; Blue Star; First Investors; SNET; Beefsteak Charlie's; Hebrew National; Hallmark; Ch. 7; AAA; Ladies Home Journal; Cohen's; Evian; Lillet Wine; Cheerwine; American Service Centers; Frosty Paws; KDKA; Citibank). Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 31:00 (Box AV3)
  - Demos
    - Alpine Lace Cheese: Korean Deli. 1991. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 2:00, 2 tapes (Box AV3)
    - Change. 1988. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 150:00, 5 tapes (Box AV3)
    - Reel 12 (Frobel; Granada TV Rental; Pevely; Bryant Park; Partnership for a Drug Free America; SNET; Beefsteak Charlie's; KABC; Eagle Snacks; AAA; Ladies' Home Journal; La Cage Aux Folles; Goldstar; First Investors; Cohen's; Evian; Hallmark; Hebrew National; Blue Star). Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 29:00 (Box AV4)
    - Reel 16. 1991. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV4)
    - Reel 20 alternate version (Frobel; KPIX; Eagle Snacks; Pevely; Partnership for a Drug Free America; Granada TV Rental; Carlsberg; La Cage Aux Folles; KPIX; Bryant Park Restoration Society). 1991. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 11:00 (Box AV4)
    - Reel 21 alternate version (Automatic Data Processing; Allie's BBQ; Levi 501; Milkbone; Burroughs-Wellcome; Entertainment Tonight; Blue Cross Blue Shield; Love Connection; Catskills on Broadway). 1994. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV4)
    - Reel 23 (Shell Gasoline; Entertainment Tonight; Regina Porter Clothes; Supercharger; Milkbone; Shoetown; Love Connectin; Allie's BBQ; SNET; Channel Home Centers; Alpine Lace Cheese; Catskills on Broadway). 1994. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 13:00 (Box AV4)
    - Formula Shell, 12 spots. 1995. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 12:00 (Box AV4)
    - Frobel Finals, 20 spots. Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 20:00 (Box AV4)
    - Hair Care Harmony: Valley Girl 2. 1987. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV4)
    - Mastercard: Haircut voiceover. 1989. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV4)
    - Warner's Semi-Annual Sale, 12 spots. 1991. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 12:00 (Box AV4)
    - Worried/Mary Hart/Happy 10th (ABC Radio Network). 1991. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 8:00 (Box AV4)
  - Music and Lyrics
    - Comedy/Lyric reel. 1985. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 60:00, 3 tapes (Box AV4)
    - Joy's Comedy and Music. Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV4)
    - Lyric reel. 1984. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 20:00 (Box AV4)
    - Lyric and comedy reel 3. 1985. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 40:00, 2 tapes (Box AV4)
    - Part of Sell It With Music. Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 20:00 (Box AV4)
  - Speeches
    - 92nd St. Y (Frobel; Eagle Snacks; Beefsteak Charlie's; Carlsberg; Pevely; Ladies' Home Journal; Granada TV Rental; La Cage Aux Folles; Perdue; Blue Nun; Nichols & May; Orkin's; Bob and Ray; Jack Benny). 1987. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 22:00 (Box AV5)
    - Advertising Age (Eagle Snacks; Frobel; Granada TV Rental; Hebrew National; USA Network; Pevely Dairy; Evian; Goldstar; Cohen's Fashion Optical; Perdue Chicken; Blue Nun; Nichols & May; Dick Orkin; Bob and Ray; Stan Freeberg; Bryant Park Restoration). 1987. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 20:00 (Box AV5)
    - Creative Circle (Jack Benny). 1987. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 20:00 (Box AV5)
    - Creative Circle (Eagle Snacks; Frobel; Pevely; Granada TV Rental; La Cage Aux Folles; Blue Star; Dunkin Donuts; SNET; Coca-Cola; Perdue; Blue Nun; Nichols & May; Orkin; Bob and Ray; Stan Freeberg; Bert and Barz). 1989. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 21:00 (Box AV5)
    - Doctors (Laughing Cow; Eagle Snacks; Hebrew National; Blue Star; Gloria Parker; Valley Girl; Goldstar; Granada TV Rental; Stressbusters; Perdue; SNET; Jefferson Bank). Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 12:00 (Box AV5)
    - Friar's (Stan Freeberg; Craving; Art Collector; Lanie's Wedding; Catskills Aunt Lil; Mabel Blue Cross; VG1; Columbus Ave.; Dear Jerry Herman; Doctor Catskills). 1993. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 11:00 (Box AV5)
    - Late in My Life (Scott Jarvis). 1985. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV5)
    - London (15 spots). Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 15:00 (Box AV5)
    - Long Island Ad Club (14 spots). 1992. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 14:00 (Box AV5)
    - Milan (15 spots). 1994. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 15:00 (Box AV5)
    - Ottowa (Eagle Snacks; Fromageries Bel; Pevely; Haagen Dazs; KPIX; Blue Cross Blue Shield of New Jersey; Catskills on Broadway). 1992. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 11:00 (Box AV5)
    - San Antonio. 1998. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV5)
    - Speech reel (Eagle Snacks; Frobel; Pevely; SNET; La Cage Aux Folles; Cohen's Fashion Optical; Granada TV Rental; Beefsteak Charlie's; Frank Perdue; Blue Nun; Nichols & May; Dick Orkin; Bob & Ray; Stan Freeberg; Bryant Park Restoration). 1987. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 19:00 (Box AV5)
    - Speech reel (Frobel; Pevely; Cohen's Fashion Optical; SNET; La Cage Aux Folles; Granada TV Rental; Pitney Bowes; Beefsteak Charlie's; Eagle Snacks; Jack Benny). 1987. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 15:00 (Box AV5)
    - Toronto. 1997. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 20:00 (Box AV5)
  - Commercials
    - Colgate. Undated. Format: 16mm. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV5)
    - Colgate: Cold Power. Undated. Format: 16mm. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV5)
    - Compilation (Invisible Man; Hebrew National; ESS; Maxi; Fleischmann's; Channel; Abe Beame; Playtex panty hose; Douche; Colgate Woman Sport; Catherine Deneuve spots; Joy Golden). Undated. Format: 16mm. TRT: 20:00 (Box AV5)
    - Fleischmann's: Marty. Undated. Format: 16mm. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV5)
    - Happiness: Jetty. Undated. Format: 16mm. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV5)
    - Singer: Smiling Sally. Undated. Format: 16mm. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV5)
  - Radio Spots
    - Challengers: Mom & Audrey; Sol & Barney; Lovers. 1990. Format: 1/4 audiotape. 1:30, 2 tapes (Box AV6)
    - Challengers: Sol & Barney final. 1990. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV6)
    - Challengers/Phil Donahue: Concierge; Big Change; Ma & Audrey; Adele Writes to Phil. 1990. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 6:30 (Box AV6)
    - Family Feud: Where's Ray Colmes? 1990. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV6)
    - Frobel: Shower. 1986. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV6)
    - Frobel: Valley Girl IV. 1987. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV6)
    - Goldstar: Granny; Interpreter; Desmond. Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV6)
    - Group W (Mercury Awards): Enid Returns. 1992. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV6)
    - Haagen Dazs: Bradley Frumkis. 1992. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV6)
    - Haagen Dazs: Vanilla. 1992. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV6)
    - Hair Care Harmony: Valley Girl 2. Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV6)
    - Hebrew National: Forgotten Salami; American Dreams; Renaissance Art; In the Poconos. 1985. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV6)
    - Hebrew National: Forgotten Salami; American Dreams; In the Poconos. 1986. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV6)
    - Indy News/Indy Star/Matchline: Interview. 1994. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV6)
    - Inside Edition (WNBC): Older Man. Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV6)
    - KPIX-TV: Tabloid TV; Sex Sox Saks; Mall Talk; Get a Goldfish. 1989. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV6)
    - KYW-TV/Current Affair: Creatures of Habit. 1990. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV6)
    - KYW-TV/Hunter: No More Talk. 1992. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV6)
    - La Cage Aux Folles: Dear Arthur Laurents. 1985. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV6)
    - La Cage Aux Folles: Dear Jerry Harmon. 1985. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV6)
    - La Cage Aux Folles: Van Johnson; Jerry Harmon; Arthur Laurents. 1985. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV6)
    - Levi 501, 7 spots. 1990. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 7:00 (Box AV6)
    - Mastercard: Haircut; Ad. 1989. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV6)
    - MCI: Dude; Super Model; Lottery Commission; President. 1993. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV6)
    - Meadowlands: Anniversary; Friday Night. 1992. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV6)
    - Meadowlands: Anniversary/St. Patrick's Day. 1993. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV6)
    - Mercury Awards: Harvey. 1993. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV6)
    - Milkbone: Best Buddy; Perfect Guy; Wet Nose; What an Animal. 1993. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV6)
    - Monmouth Park: Opening Day; Proposal. 1992. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV6)
    - Joy Golden interview, Channel 11, Best Talk in Town. 1986. Format: VHS. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV6)
    - Love 94-FM: Greg; Allison; Ellen; Xavier. Undated. Format: VHS. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV6)
    - Monmouth Park: Parason/Opening Day; Diamond Jim. 1993. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV7)
    - Morgan's Honey Mustard Salad Dressing: Bear. 1990. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV7)
    - Multiple Schlerosis Read-a-Thon: Midget. Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV7)
    - NBC/Love Connection and Ruckus: Bad Connection; Good Connection; Contestant. 1991. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV7)
    - Nivea: Boys; Moving; Bathtime. 1990. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV7)
    - North Fork Bank: No's. 1994. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV7)
    - Northwest Natural Gas: Cure for Procrastination; Mona. 1994. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV7)
    - Nutrisystem: Carmen Miranda. 1991. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV7)
    - NY Style Bagel Chips: Anniversary; Cocktail Party; Frankie. 1995. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV7)
    - Opti-Free: Opera. 1992. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV7)
    - Pealer's Flowers: 2000 Carats; Chance Meeting. 1991. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV7)
    - Pealer's Flowers: Pop remix. 1991. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV7)
    - Pizza Hut: 11 spots. 1986. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 8:30 (Box AV7)
    - Pizza Hut finals: 11 spots. Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 7:45 (Box AV7)
    - Pizza Hut Lunch Pizza: Can't Wait; Great Food Fast; Early Lunch; Inventory; Working Too Hard. 1986. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 4:30 (Box AV7)
    - Regina Porter Clothes: Spiritual Awakening. 1994. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV7)
    - Riscassi & Davis: Tough Questions. 1993. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV7)
    - Riscassi & Davis: Tough World. 1991. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV7)
    - Roy Rogers: Take Out Chicken. 1989. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 0:50 (Box AV7)
    - Shell Atlanta Re-Entry: Shell Be Comin'; Dipstick. 1994. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV7)
    - Shell/ETD: Extraterrestrial; Member ETD; Transmogrifying Device; Band from Seattle. 1994. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:30 (Box AV7)
    - Shell Rotella Oil: Rainy Night; Lady Trucker. 1993. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV7)
    - Shoe Town: Friends. 1992. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV7)
    - Shoe Town: Straight Sell; Friends. 1992. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 8:00 (Box AV7)
    - Short Circuit II: Girls; Boys. 1988. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV7)
    - SNET: Phil's Office; Mom Rents. 1994. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV7)
    - SNET: Uncle Phil's Gift; How Many?; Barb's Gift; Last Minute. 1992. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 2:30 (Box AV7)
    - SNET Holiday Catalog: Good Will; Ben; Ben's Surprise. 1993. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV7)
    - Supercharger: Wedding. Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV7)
    - Thighmaster Plus: Ruthie. 1993. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV7)
    - Tony Awards. 1990. Format: VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
    - Warnaco IPO video: Corporate Video. 1992. Format: VHS. TRT: 3:27 (Box AV7)
    - Work portfolio: Television reel (7 commercials). Undated. Format: VHS. TRT: 7:00 (Box AV7)
    - Various Production: CBS; Allie's Bar-B-Cue; Wild Turkey; Restaurant Associates. 1990. Format: VHS. TRT: 5:30 (Box AV8)
    - Various Production: Avenue at Tower City; Alouette Cheese; Choice Care HMO; Wild Turkey Bourbon (Australia); Old Tyme Soft Drinks; Allie's Bar-B-Cue; Roy Rogers; Burroughs-Wellcome HIV testing. 1990. Format: VHS. TRT: 9:00 (Box AV8)
    - Vlasic Pickles/Wiejeske Wyroby/Milwaukee's Pickles: Billy Bob; State Fair. 1993. Format: VHS. TRT: 1:30 (Box AV8)
    - Volvic Water: Shrinking World; Sounds of…; Rush Hour. 1994. Format: VHS. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV8)
    - Warner's Just Your Fit: Right Here Right Now. 1991. Format: VHS. TRT: 1:30, 2 tapes (Box AV8)
    - A Few Jingles from Yore (Eagle Snacks; Coors; Danskin; Caesar's; Visa; Max Factor). Undated. Format: CD-R. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV8)
    - Apple and Eve auditions. 2003. Format: CD-R. TRT: 20:00 (Box AV8)
    - Joy Radio Casting. Undated. Format: CD-R. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV8)
    - Mercury Awards, Radio's Top 40 for 1991. 1992. Format: CD-R. TRT: 40:00 (Box AV8)
    - Caldor: Veteran's Day, Thanksgiving, Christmas spots. 1997. Format: DAT. TRT: 34:00 (Box AV8)
    - Frobel Laughing Cow: Red Jogging Hat; Uncle Hal; Ha Ha Moo Moo; Business Meeting; Cookie and Alfred. 1998. Format: DAT. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV8)
    - London Workshop reel. 1995. Format: DAT. TRT: 15:00 (Box AV8)
    - Sell It With Music. Undated. Format: DAT. TRT: 60:00 (Box AV8)
    - Tropical Freezes: Anniversary. 1997. Format: DAT. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV8)
    - Tropical Freezes: Ma's Visit. 1997. Format: DAT. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV8)
  - Television
    - Demo reel. 1985. Format: Umatic. TRT: 7:30 (Box AV8)
    - Danskin/Starskin: Everybody Wants to Be a Star. Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV8)
    - Danskin Bras and Panties: Tennis. 1983. Format: Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV8)
    - Frobel: Valley Girl. 1988. Format: Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV8)
    - J&J Reach: Go Too Far. 1981. Format: Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV8)
    - J&J Reach: Unconventional Weapon. 1981. Format: Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV8)
    - Playtex Made for Me Bra: Guess My Size. 1983. Format: Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV8)
    - Say It with Music. Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV8)
    - Visa: New Baby. 1983. Format: Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV8)
    - Voiceover master reel (Includes Talon Zippers; Hebrew National; Egg Beaters; Maxi Mascara; Chanel; Love94; Frobel). 1993. Format: Umatic. TRT: 20:00 (Box AV8)
    - AAF Bob Guccione Roast. 1994. Format: VHS. TRT: 90:00 (Box AV8)
    - FNN. 1991. Format: VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV8)
    - Friar's Club. Undated. Format: VHS. TRT: 90:00 (Box AV8)
    - Fromageries Bel (Frobel): Stuart; Valley Girl. Undated. Format: VHS. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV8)
    - Good Day. 1989. Format: VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV8)
    - Radio Advertising Bureau: Imagery Transfer, Radio Extends Your TV Campaign. 1997. Format: VHS. TRT: 10:30 (Box AV8)
    - Work portfolio: Amtrak spot. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV8)
    - Work portfolio: Fleischmann's Alex spot.Undated. Format: 16mm. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV8)
    - Work portfolio: Singer spot.Undated. Format: 16mm. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV8)
  - Audition tapes
    - AAA: Stuck in Snow; Flat at Midnight. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV9)
    - AAAA: Upward Mobility; Father. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV9)
    - ABC: Ellen Burstyn Show. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - ADP. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV9)
    - ALCON. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV9)
    - ALCON. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV9)
    - ALCON: Older Women. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - ALCON: Phone Call. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - ALCON: Relationship. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - Allerest. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - Allerest. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV9)
    - Allerest: Dr. B; Interview; Allergy Blues; Jewish Mom. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV9)
    - Allerest: Interview. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - Allerest: Jewish Mother. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - Allerest: Jewish Mother. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV9)
    - Allie's BBQ audition. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV9)
    - Allie's BBQ casting. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 60:00, 2 tapes (Box AV9)
    - Alpine Lace Cheese: Italian auditions. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV9)
    - Alpine Lace Cheese: Italian Deli. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV9)
    - Alpine Lace Cheese: Korean; Indian; Martin; Jewish. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV9)
    - Alpine Lace Cheese: Korean; Jewish final. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00, 2 tapes (Box AV9)
    - Alpine Lace Cheese: Macho Guys; Tough Cookie. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00, 2 tapes (Box AV9)
    - Alpine Lace Cheese: Pookins. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV9)
    - Alpine Lace Cheese: Vinnie's Deli; Martin's Deli. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV9)
    - American Home Products/Preparation H. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV9)
    - AT&T: You're the Top; Mother's Day. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV9)
    - Atlantis Casino. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV9)
    - Au Bon Pain/Carlsberg. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV9)
    - Au Bon Pain: Fabulous Lunch. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV9)
    - Au Bon Pain: Rendezvous. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - Babies R Us. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV9)
    - Bauerlein. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV9)
    - Benihana. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV9)
    - Best TV promos. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV9)
    - Blue Cross Blue Shield of N.J.: Barbecue; Music. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:30 (Box AV9)
    - Blue Cross Blue Shield of N.J.: Mabel. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - Blue Cross Blue Shield of N.J.: rough scratch tracks. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00, 2 tapes (Box AV9)
    - Blue Cross Blue Shield of N.J.: Sue Frost. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV9)
    - Blue Cross Blue Shield of N.J.: Tina. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - Blue Star Foods: Dining Lite. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV9)
    - Boar's Head. 2002. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 13:00 (Box AV9)
    - Budweiser/LA Beer. 1984. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00, 2 tapes (Box AV9)
    - Burroughs Wellcome: HIV Testing. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV9)
    - Burroughs Wellcome: HIV Testing. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV9)
    - Café du Jour: Date. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV9)